easywebinarplugin.com 2013-11-06

# Privacy Policy | Easy Webinar Plugin

CSZ Corporation is committed to protecting your privacy. This Statement of Privacy applies to the CSZ Corporation website and governs data collection and usage. By using the CSZ Corporation website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

Collection of your Personal Information

CSZ Corporation collects personally identifiable information, such as your e-mail address, name, home and/or work address and/or telephone number. CSZ Corporation also collects anonymous demographic information, which is not unique to you, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, preferences, interests and favorites.

There is also information about your computer hardware and software that is automatically collected by CSZ Corporation. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by CSZ Corporation for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the CSZ Corporation website.

In the event that you contact us for customer support through the website, we may also request that you provide additional User Information relevant to the support requested by you. Users are under no obligation to provide such information. However, we cannot guarantee that we can provide customer support in the event that relevant information related to the use of our products or services is withheld. We may retain communications relating to customer support, and/or information drawn from such communications, for statistical and/or reference purposes.

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through CSZ Corporation public message boards or forums, this information may be collected and used by others. Note: CSZ Corporation does not read your private online communications with others.

CSZ Corporation encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from CSZ Corporation so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. CSZ Corporation is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the CSZ Corporation 

Use of your Personal Information

CSZ Corporation collects and uses your personal information to operate the CSZ Corporation website and deliver the services you have requested. CSZ Corporation may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from CSZ Corporation and its affiliates. CSZ Corporation may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services.

CSZ Corporationdoes not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. CSZ Corporation> may, from time to time, contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. In those cases, your unique personally identifiable information (e-mail, name, address, telephone number) is not transferred to the third party. In addition, CSZ Corporation> may share data with trusted partners to help us perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. Such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to CSZ Corporation, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

CSZ Corporation does not use or disclose sensitive personal information, such as race, religion, or political affiliations, without your explicit consent.

CSZ Corporation keeps track of the websites and pages you visit within CSZ Corporation, in order to determine what CSZ Corporation services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising within CSZ Corporation to customers whose behavior indicates that they are interested in a particular subject area.

CSZ Corporation websites will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on CSZ Corporation or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of CSZ Corporation (including enforcing this agreement); and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of CSZ Corporation, or the public.

Use of Cookies

The CSZ Corporation website use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies are not used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize CSZ Corporation pages, or register with CSZ Corporation site or services, a cookie helps CSZ Corporation to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same CSZ Corporation website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the CSZ Corporation features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the CSZ Corporation services or websites you visit.

If you provide CSZ Corporation with user information, you have the following rights with respect to that information:

  * To review the user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that we correct any errors, outdated information, or omissions in user information that you have supplied to us
  * To request that your user information not be used to contact you
  * To request that your user information be removed from any solicitation list that we use
  * To request that your user information be deleted from our records and
  * To opt out of being solicited by this website or third parties

If you request that your user information be deleted from our records, there may be a brief delay in our processing that request, while verify that the request is valid and originates from you as opposed to an unauthorized third party. If you request that your information be deleted, we reserve the right to terminate and/or limit your access to the CSZ Corporation website.

To exercise any of these rights, please contact us at [support@caseyzemanonline.com](mailto:support@caseyzemanonline.com)

Security of your Personal Information

No method of safeguarding information is 100% secure. CSZ Corporation uses a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. CSZ Corporation secures the personally identifiable information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

Changes to this Statement

CSZ Corporation will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. CSZ Corporation encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how CSZ Corporation is protecting your information. When such a change is made, we will update the "Last Updated" date above. 

Enforcement of this Privacy Statement

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should first contact us at [support@caseyzemanonline.com](mailto:support@caseyzemanonline.com). If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or we have not addressed your inquiry to your satisfaction, you should then contact us at support@caseyzemanonline.com 

To Unsubscribe From CSZ Corporation

You may unsubscribe from CSZ Corporation marketing communications by clicking on the "unsubscribe" link located on the bottom of the company's emails. Additionally, you may unsubscribe by contacting CSZ Corporation

Contact Information

CSZ Corporation welcomes your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that CSZ Corporation has not adhered to this Statement, please contact CSZ Corporation at support@caseyzemanonline.com. We will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly determine and remedy the problem. 

CSZ Corporation is located at

5482 Wilshire Blvd, Suite 1642,  
Los Angeles, Ca 90036,  
Phone 323 230 6403 Fax 323 230 5428.
